coorslight.com 2017-07-17

# Privacy Policy | Coors Light

## _COORS BREWING COMPANY PRIVACY POLICY_

Coors Brewing Company respects the privacy of every individual who visits our websites or responds to online advertisements or e-mail campaigns. The information that you share with us will be treated with appropriate care. This Privacy Policy describes our policies on the collection, use, and disclosure of your information in connection with your use of our websites, social media pages, emails, and mobile applications (“Site” or “Sites”), as well as through our online advertisements at other websites and e-mail campaigns. This Privacy Policy will also provide you with instructions on how to opt out of sharing information about you with us.

Information collected on this Site may be used in the manner described below by Coors Brewing Company and its affiliated brands, our agents, subsidiaries, trusted service partners, and corporate affiliates acting on our behalf (collectively, “Coors Brewing Company”). When used in this Privacy Policy, the terms “we,” “us,” and “our” refer to Coors Brewing Company.

We encourage you to read the entire Privacy Policy. Please click on any of the links below to review that particular section.

Scope

Access Restricted to People of Legal Drinking Age

Types of Information We Collect

How We Collect Your Information

Use of Your Information

Sharing Your Information

Social Networks/Online Communities

Choice/Opt-Out

Security

Linked Sites

Additional Information

Your California Privacy Rights

Changes to this Privacy Policy

Privacy Inquiries and Correcting Your Information

#### _**SCOPE**_

This Privacy Policy applies to the information we obtain from individuals interacting with Coors Brewing Company and its Sites, products, and services. It does not apply to information we obtain in our capacity as an employer.

#### _**ACCESS RESTRICTED TO PEOPLE OF LEGAL DRINKING AGE**_

**Coors Brewing Company SITES, INCLUDING ACCESS TO ALL ADVERTISING AND MARKETING INFORMATION ON THE SITES, ARE INTENDED ONLY FOR PERSONS OF LEGAL DRINKING AGE. DATE OF BIRTH VERIFICATION IS REQUIRED AT THE ENTRANCE OF THE SITE AND AGE VERIFICATION PROMPTS MAY ALSO BE LOCATED WITHIN THE SITES. IF YOU BELIEVE SOMEONE UNDER THE LEGAL DRINKING AGE HAS PROVIDED US WITH INFORMATION BY OBTAINING ACCESS IN VIOLATION OF THE SITES' ACCESS RESTRICTIONS, PLEASE[CONTACT US](http://www.coorslight.com/contact) IMMEDIATELY AND THIS INFORMATION WILL BE REMOVED. **

#### _**TYPES OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT**_

The types of information that Coors Brewing Brewing Company collects about you may include:

  * Contact information such as name, street address, email address, and telephone or mobile number;

  * Billing information such as credit card number and billing address;

  * Demographic information such as date of birth, gender, interests, state, country, and zip code;

  * Unique identifiers such as user name and password;

  * Preference and other information such as product wish lists, order history, marketing preferences, and cell phone carrier;

  * Information you provide in public forums on our Sites and Applications and information you provide to us when you use our Applications on third-party websites or platforms such as social networking sites;

  * Location information such as your actual or approximate location;

  * Usage, viewing, and technical data, including your device identifier or IP address; and

  * Social Security Number (in limited circumstances, for example if you win a sweepstakes or receive compensation that must be reported on government tax forms).

#### _**HOW WE COLLECT YOUR INFORMATION**_

Coors Brewing Company may obtain information about you from a number of sources to which you provide information or from which you agree we may access your information, including but not limited to: our Sites, social media platforms (i.e., Facebook), mobile applications, third-party partners or vendors, at sponsored events, or through surveys, sweepstakes or promotional entries, or our customer call centers.

  1. ##### Mobile Applications

When you download a Coors Brewing Company mobile application to your mobile device (“Applications”) there may be an opportunity for you to provide us with your information. If you choose to share any information with us, we will store it, use it, and share it only in ways that are described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy shall govern any information collected by us as a result of your use of the Applications (if any).

Some Applications may collect precise information about the location of your mobile device via the geolocation functionality of your mobile device. You will be given an opportunity to opt in to the collection of this location-based data before it is collected. You may at any time opt out of the collection of location data either through the Application’s settings, or by uninstalling the Application through the uninstall process. 

Please note, certain practices are outside of our control and you should always read and understand the policies of any third party provider, such as Google with respect to Android Applications and Apple with respect to iOS Applications, and your wireless carrier, before making any purchase or downloading any Applications.  

  2. ##### Tracking Technologies

Coors Brewing Company Sites use “cookies” or other tracking devices which may collect, but is not limited to, the following information: demographic data, browser type, IP address, pages viewed, activity conducted on the page, and the timing of your visit. By visiting our Sites you consent to the collection of this information by Coors Brewing Company, our trusted service partners and permitted third parties.  

You may refuse or delete cookies on our Sites. Please refer to your browser Help instructions to learn more about cookies and other tracking devices and how to manage their use. If you choose to refuse or delete cookies, some of the functionality of our Sites may be impaired.  If you use another computer or change browsers you will need to repeat the process of refusing or deleting cookies.

For information on how to opt-out of the collection of information by other tracking devices please refer to the “Choice/Opt-Out” section below.   

Coors Brewing Company, our trusted service partners and permitted third parties may also advertise our products on third-party websites. Third-party websites may also use cookies or other tracking devices. Coors Brewing Company, our trusted service partners and permitted third parties do not have control over the tracking technologies utilized by third-party websites. As such, you should carefully review the privacy policies of those third-party sites to understand their tracking activities, if any.

    1. ##### Google

      1. ##### Website Analytics

Coors Brewing Company Sites may use Google Analytics to collect information about your use of our website. This information consists of information that your web browser automatically sends to Google, such as the web address of the page that you visit and your IP address. Google may also set cookies or read preexisting cookies. This information is stored on Google´s servers. Google uses this information to provide us with reports about traffic to our website and your visit to our website (such as the domain from which you access the internet, the web address of the website from which you linked to our site, the time and date of your visit to the web pages that you view and click through). We use this data to improve our website structure and content.

Google may also use this data in accordance with their Privacy Policy, which can be found at <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>. For more detailed information on how Google uses your data through our website, please visit <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/>.

You may opt-out of our use of Google Analytics by visiting the _Google Analytics opt-out page_ and installing the Google Analytics browser add-on, currently made available by Google at <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

      2. ##### Advertising Features

Coors Brewing Sites may also use the following Google Analytics Advertising Features:  Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting **.** Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting uses a third party cookie to collect information about our website traffic by tracking users across websites and across time, which generates a report for us to better understand our website users.  

If you do not want Google to collect and use this information you may visit the Google Ad Settings page (<http://www.google.com/safetycenter/tools/#manage-your-ads-preferences>) or you can also visit the website <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices> as referenced above to change your consumer preferences with respect to certain online ads and to obtain further information about third party ad networks and online behavioral advertising.  For the Google Analytics Advertising Features, you may also opt-out of our use of Google Analytics as described above.  Please remember that changing your settings with certain browsers and ad networks will not carry your privacy choices across browsers and other ad networks. 

    2. ##### Quantcast

Coors Brewing Company also uses Quantcast to help us understand the characteristics and demographics of the people who visit our Sites. Per Quantcast’s privacy policy, Quantcast collects information about your use of our website through connecting information that your web address automatically sends, such as the web address of the page that you visit and browser time or type, with a random identifier (a cookie ID). This information is then analyzed to improve our Sites and products. Quantcast’s privacy policy states that they do not link this data to your name, address, email or phone number, or otherwise attempt to discover your identity. For further information on how Quantcast works you can visit their site at Quantcast.com. In order to “Opt-Out” of Quantcast go to <https://www.quantcast.com/opt-out>.

  3. ##### Ad Networks

We use third party ad networks (called third-party ad servers or network advertisers) to deliver ads to you on our behalf. These third party ad networks may place their cookies, web beacons or other technology on our Sites or Applications or in your browser to collect information about you when you visit this Website or use this Application (such as browser type, time and date, browsing or transaction activity, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over, or a platform-provided identifier during your visits to this and other websites) to enable those third party ad networks to deliver to you advertisements on third party websites and mobile applications for our products or services or those of third parties that are likely to be of greater interest to you.

We encourage you to view the privacy policy of advertisers and ad services to learn more about their cookies and other technologies.  To learn more about interest-based advertising, or to opt-out, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/>.

If you do not want to receive those kinds of advertisements, look for the "Ad Choices" icon in the advertisements, which will contain a link to the privacy policy of the ad network that will provide you with information on how to opt-out of receiving such targeted advertising.

You can also visit the website [http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) to change your consumer preferences with respect to certain online ads and to obtain further information about third party ad networks and online behavioral advertising.

  4. ##### Do Not Track Technologies

We will automatically collect cookies and other information when you visit the Site.  Due to this automatic collection, we do not currently honor “do not track” requests.  We currently participate in third party ad networks and use third party cookies as discussed above to track your visits across websites.

  5. ##### Transactions

You may purchase merchandise from some of our Sites. This Privacy Policy applies to any information you provide in connection with any such purchases. In some instances, you may be directed to a third-party website to initiate your transaction. These third-party websites will be clearly identified and link to their own privacy policies so you know which company is collecting your information. You should refer to those policies for any privacy-related concerns regarding your purchase with them.

#### _**USE OF YOUR INFORMATION**_

We or one of our trusted service partners may use your information to:

  * Send you requested product or service information;

  * Fulfill your order;

  * Send you an order confirmation;

  * Provide customer support;

  * Administer your account;

  * Send you marketing communications;

  * Administer promotions and sweepstakes you enter and notify you of the results;

  * Customize and improve communication content;

  * Conduct marketing research and analysis;

  * Display content based upon your location and/or interests; or

  * Comply with or enforce applicable legal requirements, agreements, and policies.

We may also use your information for other purposes on an anonymized basis, or as otherwise required by law.

From time to time, certain pages on our Sites permit visitors to forward information from one of our Sites to another person. This information may only be shared with persons of legal drinking age. If your email address, social media username or other information is submitted through use of this functionality, you may receive an e-mail or communication at the request and direction of a visitor via an automatic technical process even though you may have previously indicated that you do not want to receive email or communications from us. Please note that such emails or communications are sent by and at the direction of the Site visitor, not Coors Brewing Company, and your receipt of such emails or communications is not a violation of this Privacy Policy. Coors Brewing Company does not collect or retain third-party email addresses, social media usernames or other information submitted through this functionality.

#### _**SHARING YOUR INFORMATION**_

We will share your information with appropriate third parties in the ways that are described in this Privacy Policy. We may use your information to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, improve our products and services, better understand customer interests and preferences, and /or provide you relevant information. We may provide your information to trusted service partners for research, analytical and marketing purposes, and/or to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other businesses or persons that help us with our business activities (e.g., processing credit card transactions, administering sweepstakes and contests, shipping your order, assisting us in Site operations, providing customer service, delivering email communications, etc.) or that assist us in improving our products, content, services, or advertising.

Coors Brewing Company or persons that help us with our business activities, are authorized to use your aforementioned information **only** as necessary to provide these services.

For example, Coors Brewing Company may share the information it collects about you in the following instances:

  * As required by law, such as in conjunction with a government inquiry or to comply with a subpoena or similar legal process;

  * When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request;

  * With our trusted service partners for our marketing activities or to conduct joint marketing programs;

  * With our trusted service partners who work on our behalf and who do not have an independent right to use the information to which they have access or that we disclose to them;

  * In connection with a corporate change including a merger, acquisition, or sale of assets;

  * Within Coors Brewing Company and its affiliates; and

  * To any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

On certain of our Sites we may enable you to access online communities for sharing information such as messages, photos, and videos. You may only share this information with persons of legal drinking age. We may also enable you to post content from some of our Sites to your profile on other social networks. Please be aware that the privacy policy of the social networking site will apply to any content you post on or provide to that Site.

In addition, when you post or share content or communications from our Sites with any third party social network you also allow us to share information with that third party social network. We cannot control any policies or terms of such third party social networks.  As a result, we cannot be responsible for any use of your information or content by a third party social network, which you use at your own risk.

  1. ##### Facebook

Our Sites may allow you to connect and share information with Facebook. Sharing such information with Facebook may require us to implement cookies and/or APIs in order to facilitate the communication between our Sites and Facebook. That information, shared through cookies and/or API’s, then becomes subject to Facebook’s Data Policy, located at <https://www.facebook.com/full_data_use_policy>. 

#### _**CHOICE/OPT-OUT**_

If you have already submitted information to us and would like us to remove it from our records, please [contact us](http://www.coorslight.com/contact) and request removal of the information from our records. Once we receive your request, we will remove the information you provided to Coors Brewing Company from our files.

If you wish to have an e-mail address removed from our records, please [click here](https://unsubscribe.coorslight.com/).You may also choose to stop receiving updates or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in emails you receive from us.

If you choose to join a mobile marketing list, please be aware that there are usually costs associated with receiving SMS (text) or MMS (multimedia) messages depending on your wireless carrier and plan. You should check with your mobile carrier to determine what charges apply before signing up to receive our updates via your mobile phone. If you would like to stop receiving messages from us on your mobile phone, please reply to the message with “STOP.” You may also contact your mobile carrier for additional information on receiving or stopping mobile messages.

For more information on how to opt out of our use of Google Analytics and our use of its Advertising Features please visit <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout> and <http://www.google.com/safetycenter/tools/#manage-your-ads-preferences>.

For more information on to opt out of Quantcast, you can visit their site at <https://www.quantcast.com/opt-out>.

Users can opt out of additional tracking and targeted advertising, including Google Analytics and Quantcast, via the Digital Advertising Alliance’s (DAA) opt-out page and the Networking Advertising Initiatives’ (NAI) opt-out page at <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/> and <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>, respectively.

If you have previously enabled your computer or mobile device to send us location information, you may be able to opt out from further allowing us to access such information by changing the settings on your computer or mobile device or by uninstalling the Application.

#### _**SECURITY**_

The security, integrity, and confidentiality of your information are extremely important to us. Coors Brewing Company uses administrative, technical, and physical security to protect the information we maintain to ensure that it is used according to this Privacy Policy. Please be aware though that, despite our best efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable.

#### _**LINKED SITES**_

Coors Brewing Sites may contain links to third-party websites not controlled by Coors Brewing Company or covered by this Privacy Policy. If you submit information to any of those websites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website you visit.

Please note that if you provide information to us via a social media site or participate in a social media site linked to the Website, you consent to our use of your information for any reason as if it were submitted to us directly via the Website.

#### _**ADDITIONAL  INFORMATION**_

Our Sites may include interactive programs that provide specific services from another company, such as “liking” or sharing content, often referred to as widgets. You may have the opportunity to submit information, such as your email address, for collection through a widget. A widget may also use cookies and/or collect usage data. Information collected by a widget is governed by the privacy policy of the company that created it.

#### _**YOUR  CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**_

If you are a California resident, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 provides you the right to receive (a) information identifying any third party(ies) to whom we may have disclosed, within the preceding calendar year, your information for that third party’s direct marketing purposes; and (b) a description of the categories of information disclosed. To obtain such information free of charge, please [contact us.](http://www.coorslight.com/contact)

#### _**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**_

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time by posting additions or modifications to this page, so we encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy.

**Last Modified and Effective Date** :  August 2016

To help you stay current of any changes, we take the following two steps: (i) we not the date the Privacy Policy was last updated above; (ii) when we make a change to the Privacy  Policy, we post conspicuous announcement of such changes on the homepage of the Website next to the link to this Privacy Policy. Your use of the Website following the posting of any revised Privacy Policy shall be deemed acceptance of the revised policy, so we strongly recommend that you check back to the Privacy Policy periodically.

#### _**PRIVACY INQUIRIES AND  CORRECTING YOUR INFORMATION**_

If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, or wish to update, correct, or remove your information, please [contact us](http://www.coorslight.com/contact) or write to us at:

 Coors Brewing Company Attn: Legal Department

 250 South Wacker Drive

 Chicago IL 60606

Thanks for visiting Coors Brewing Company Sites.
